举起手来
Hands where I can see 'em.
你是罗伊吗
Is that you, Roy?
那你就是沃尔特了
Which makes you Walt.
（忆往昔）
乔迪·米尔斯是个好人
Jody Mills is good people,
她会给你个住的地方
and she'll give you a place to crash.
让你慢慢缓过来
until you get back on your feet.
如果你能像我希望的那么无情
If only you'd been as ruthless as I hoped.
- 现在怎么办 - 我们开始吧
- Now what? ‭- Let's begin.
贝维尔夫人真是厉害
I do have to hand it to Lady Bevell.
你的治疗非常成功
Your treatment's been most successful.
别动
Stay where you are.
我是说你
I was talking to you.
妈妈
‭Mom?
最好别动 她会开枪的
I really wouldn't move. She will shoot you.
- 你是想去哪 - 凯奇
- Where do you think you're going? - Ketch.
你们的地堡真是绝佳的堡垒
Your bunker is an excellent fortress.
还是更好的坟墓
An even better tomb.
我们对锁做了改造 切断了水
We've rejiggered the locks, we've shut off the water,
等我们走后
and once we leave,
抽入空气的泵会逆转
the pumps that bring in the air shall reverse.
你们的氧气会在
Your oxygen should be gone in…
两到三天内耗尽
two days, maybe three.
来吧 玛丽
Come along, Mary.
不
No!
（如今）
（发送至凯奇 莱斯特死了 接下来谁）
（汽修厂）
（爱达荷州 弗莱德·麦克雷 怀俄明州 科比·谢菲尔德 南达科他州 乔迪·米尔斯）
[邪恶力量 第12季第22集]
好吧 车库呢
All right. The garage?
门上有符文 墙里有钢筋
Doors are warded and the walls are reinforced steel.
好吧 或许可以从排气口出去
Okay. Um, you know, maybe we could get out through the air vents.
爬不了多远
You wouldn't get far.
管道系统里有瓶颈
There are choke points in the duct system.
我都挤不过去
not even I could squeeze through.
我们杀了她吧
I say we kill her.
你听到凯奇的话了
I mean, you heard Ketch.
我们只剩三天的空气
Said we had about three days of air left.
如果我们杀了她 还能多活一天
So if we ice her, maybe that buys us an extra day.
我向你保证 迪恩
I assure you, Dean,
我这人呼吸特别浅
I'm an extraordinarily shallow breather.
- 好吧 - 如果我们能出去
- All right. - If we ever get out of here,
是我给你们妈妈洗了脑
I am the one who programmed your mother,
所以也只有我能解除她的洗脑
which means that I am the only one who can undo it.
鉴于我猜你们会希望妈妈回来
And since I assume you want Mummy back,
你们需要我
you need me.
- 你相信她吗 - 不知道
- You believe her? - I don't know.
如果她是撒谎 好 我们干掉她
Look, if she's lying, sure, we take her out.
但妈妈还在外面 被洗脑了
But Mom is still out there, brainwashed.
如果她说的是实话 我们就需要她
If she's telling the truth, then we do need her.
好吧 你这么聪明 你说我们怎么出去
All right, you're so smart, how do we get out of here?
唯一的出路是拉动手动超控
The only way out is to pull the manual override.
- 有那么个玩意吗 - 有的
- Is that a thing? - Oh, it is.
但在地堡外面 我们够不到
But it's outside the bunker, where we can't reach it.
太棒了
Awesome.
等一下
Wait a second, guys.
我们在一个大密室里
We're in a giant vault.
这里满是神秘学书和传说
loaded down with … with occult books and lore.
这里肯定哪里有点什么
There's gotta be something somewhere in here …
一件东西 或一个咒语
an item or a spell …
什么玩意能解除封锁
some hoodoo that can reverse the lockdown.
（第一天）
我可能有发现
I think I got something.
罗姆人在欧洲被迫同化时
"When the Romani people were forced to assimilate in Europe,
罗姆人使用了一种咒语
"The, uh, the Roma used a spell,
废止仪式
"The Abrogation ritual,
作为对迫害者的反叛
as an act of rebellion against their persecutors.
罗姆教神能逆转复杂的机械过程
"The Devla turns back complex mechanical processes,
重置设备 机械
resets equipment, machinery."
- 需要什么 - 看来原料很普通
- What's it take? - Seems like pretty basic ingredients.
都是我们有的
Nothing we don't already have.
怎么了
‭What?
机械要用「处女血涂抹」
The mechanisms "must be anointed with the blood of virgins."
差得远呢
Not even close.
那好吧 我们继续查吧
All right, well, then, I guess we keep lookin'.
- 或是造假 - 什么
- Or we fake it. - ‭Excuse me?
造假
We fake it.
我这一小时以来读过不下六个净化仪式了
I mean, I've read half a dozen purification rituals in the last hour.
我们可以拿其中一个来净化我们的血
If we used one of those on … on our blood…
然后呢 把它变成处子血
Then what? Revirginize it?
或许吧
Maybe.
那我们先净化血 然后施咒
So we purify the blood, then do the spell.
两步混搭魔法
Two-step, hybrid magic.
好吧 第一步好了
All right, that's step one.
第二步 该你了
Step two, you're up.
[咒语]
起效了
It's working.
It's working!
不
No.
- 不 - 怎么回事
- No. - ‭What happened?
凯奇 他料到我们会…
Ketch! He knew we'd…
他肯定在地堡封锁机构上设置了
He must've put some kind of mystical dampener.
魔法抑制器
on the bunker's lockdown.
魔法不会起效的
Magic won't work.
（第二天）
好吧 我们试过了智取
Okay, we have… exhausted brains,
现在试试蛮力吧
so I saw we try brawn.
- 怎么做 - 墙
- How? - ‭Walls.
车库 瞭望台
Now the garage, the Crow's Nest,
这都是钢筋墙 是吧
these are all reinforced steel walls, right?
但这里 只有混凝土
But right here, that's nothing but concrete.
这里 是一条老下水管道
And right there, that's an old sewer pipe,
直通地面 超控装置
goes straight up to the surface…to the override.
等一下 那我们就…
So wait a second. We're just gonna…
肖申克一把
Straight Shawshank this bitch.
- 戴护目镜 - 戴护目镜
- Goggles? - ‭Goggles.
嗯
‭Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
我们该休息了
We earned a break.
是啊
Yeah.
我们会打通的
We'll get there.
不
No. ‭
打不通的
No, we won't.
我们至少三天才能打到地面
We're not gonna hit dirt for three days.
幸运的话两天可以
Two if we're lucky.
我知道你感觉得到 空气很稀薄了
I know you feel it … the air, it's thin.
而且越来越稀薄
And it's getting thinner.
怎么会这样
How did this happen?
哪一部分
What part?
这一切
All of it.
是啊
Yeah.
不久之前 我还觉得我们混得不错
You know, it wasn't long ago, I thought we had it made.
我们拯救了世界
We saved the world.
小卡回来了 妈妈回来了
We got Cass back. We had Mom back.
虽然不完美 但他们至少在身边
I mean, it wasn't perfect, but still, we had 'em.
而现在
And now…
现在他们都走了
Now they're all gone.
妈妈 他们对她做的事
And Mom, what they did to her…
我被他们的推销蒙蔽了
I just fell for their company line.
我
Man, I…
我看到了他们做的事 我想
I saw what they were doing, and I … and I thought,
猎人达到那样的规模 那样的合作
Hunters on that scale, working together…
我们能做多少好事啊
how much good we can do.
我一加入
And once I was in, I…
就开始盲从
I just followed.
因为那样简单
'Cause it was easy.
更简单些
Easier.
比什么简单
Easier than what?
比领导简单
Easier than leading.
你想象的结局是这样的吗
Is this how you pictured it? The end?
你知道不是的
Oh, you know it's not.
我一直以为我们会
I always thought we'd go out like…
像《虎豹小霸王》那样英勇就义
Butch and Sundance style.
是啊
Yeah.
- 荣耀光辉 - 荣耀光辉
- Blaze of glory. - ‭Blaze of glory.
我去
Son of a bitch.
你们都是疯子
You're lunatics.
这点子太蠢了
This is a colossally stupid idea.
是啊
Yep.
又大 又美
Big, beautiful,
又蠢
and dumb.
这玩意放在我这儿好久了
I've had this thing for so long.
一直在等最合适的时机使用
Been waiting for the perfect moment to use it.
爆炸可能害死我们
The explosion could kill us all.
你可能会把这整个地方震塌
You could bring the whole bloody place crashing down.
- 是啊 - 是啊
- Yeah. - ‭Yeah.
你们是疯子
You're lunatics.
喜欢动作片 爱吃芝士汉堡
Action movie-loving, cheeseburger-eating,
愚蠢的美国疯子
moronic American lunatics.
好了 美人
Okay, beautiful.
去你妈蛋
Yippee ki-yay, mother …
迪恩
Dean?
Dean!
迪恩
Dean?
好啊 疯子
Hey, lunatic.
（南达科他州 苏福尔斯 治安官）
- 玛丽 - 乔迪
- Mary? - ‭Hey, Jody.
有空吗
You got a sec?
嗯
Yeah.
没电
Dead.
Uh, dead.
这里有一个
Wait, I got one.
盖思
Garth?
天呐 听到你的声音太好了
Oh, man. It's good to hear your voice.
听着 我之前跟你说的英国人
Listen, uh, those Brits I told you about,
他们在猎杀美国猎人
they've got a hit out on American Hunters.
我猜对于狼人猎人更是如此了
I'm guessing that goes double for werewolf hunters, so…
不 我没时间解释
No, I don't have time to explain.
你和贝丝得找个安全的地方
You and Bess need to get someplace safe.
好吗 好
Okay? All right.
乔迪
Jody.
Jody?
乔迪 艾莉克斯
Jody. Alex.
她在哪
Where is she?
你们好啊
Hello, boys.
她突然袭击我时 我以为她是恶魔呢
When she clocked me out of the blue, I thought she was a demon.
真没想到洗脑能这么彻底
I had no idea that brainwashing could be so thorough.
乔迪 她…
Jody, she…
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
不怪你
It's not your fault.
幸好 艾莉克斯回家了
Fortunately, Alex came home.
我不过是替你争取了时间 是你击昏了她
All I did was buy you time. You knocked her out.
我去给你找点止痛的东西
‭I'll get you something for the pain.
来双份吧
Make it a double.
你想扮我儿子的妈妈吗
You wanna play mother to my son?
他都归你了
He's all yours.
迪恩
Dean…
那不是你妈妈
that's not your mom.
怎么了 迪恩
What's the matter, Dean?
我跟你所认识的玛丽太不一样了吗
Am I too different from the Mary you know?
还是太一样了
Or too much the same?
她来了
Here she is.
做你该做的吧
Do your thing.
好吧 你说你能治好她 治好她吧
All right, you said you could fix her, so fix her.
我
I, um…
- 我… - 她撒谎了
- Well, I - ‭She lied.
什么
What?
玛丽的洗脑
Mary's programming…
是不可逆的
It's permanent.
但你说
But you said…
你们当时要杀我
You were going to kill me.
你们所认识的玛丽 好玛丽
The Mary that you know, the good Mary,
她躲在不可穿透的心墙后面
she's hiding behind impenetrable psychic walls.
恐怕这种墙
And I'm afraid these walls…
是手榴弹打不倒的
Well, they can't be torn down with grenades.
你妈妈救不回来了
Your mother can't be saved.
好吧 「夫人」 时候到了
All right, "Lady, " time's up.
我们留你一命只有一个原因
We only kept you alive for one reason.
各位
Hey, guys.
那个 凯奇一直在给妈妈打电话
Listen, uh, Ketch keeps callin' Mom's phone.
我接吧
I'll get it.
让它接进语音信箱就行
Let it go to voicemail.
我们去后院溜达溜达
Let's take a nice little short walk to the backyard.
这不会停下的
This is not going to stop.
很快 他们会发现你们还活着 到时
Soon enough, they'll find out you're alive, and then…
如果想听我的建议 逃跑吧
Well, if you want my advice … run.
我们不会跑的
We're not running.
那你就会死
Well, then, you die.
或者
Or…
或者什么
Or what?
我们抵抗
Or we fight.
脚从桌上拿下来 杰瑞
Feet off the table, Jerry.
谢谢
Thanks.
这下应该都到了
That should be the last one.
沃尔特 罗伊
Walt. Roy.
我去
Well, damn.
我们好久没见你们了 自从
We haven't seen you guys since …
自从你们杀了我们 不介意
Since you killed us. No hard feelings.
坐吧 自便
Uh, uh, please, get comfortable.
你确定吗
Sure about this?
要不要说说叫我们来干什么
You gonna tell us what we're doing here or what?
当然 好
‭Of course. Yeah.
我和我哥哥 我们…
Um, so my … my brother and I, we … we, um…
不 告诉你们
No, you know what?
是我叫你们来的 因为
I called you here because people…
我们的人在遭到屠杀
our people, are being slaughtered.
接下来就是我们了
And we're next.
英国记录者 他们来到这里
The British Men of Letters, they came here.
因为他们认为他们能比我们更好地做我们的工作
because they thought they could do our job better than we could.
他们用他们酷炫的装备和科技诱骗了我们
And they hooked us with their flashy gear and their tech.
你们大都明智地拒绝了
Most of you had the good sense to turn 'em down.
但我没有
I didn't.
他们说他们跟我们的目标一致
They said they wanted the same thing we wanted, you know?
一个没有怪物的世界
A world free of monsters.
但那不是真话
That's not what they really wanted.
他们想要控制权
They want control.
他们想要的世界
They want to live in a world.
是他们可以坐在一个办公室里
where they can sit in some office.
决定谁可以生 谁得去死
and decide who gets to live and who gets to die.
他们杀了人
And they've killed people.
他们杀了无辜者
They've killed innocent people.
就因为他们碍了事
just because they got in the way.
他们认为为目的可以不择手段
They think the ends justify the means.
但我们知道不是的
But we know better.
我们知道猎魔并不仅仅是杀戮
We know hunting isn't just about killing.
而是做正确的事 哪怕这样很艰难
It's about doing what's right, even when it's hard.
所以我们听从直觉
So we go by our gut, right?
我们按自己的规则来 这让他们害怕
We play by our own rules, and that scares them.
这是他们要我们死的原因
That's why they want us dead,
因为我们是他们唯一控制不了的
'cause we're the one thing they can't control.
你要我们做什么
So what do you want from us?
我要你们跟随我
I want you to follow me.
打到他们家门口
Take the fight to them.
在他们出击前 干掉他们
To hit them before they hit us.
我们迅猛出击 不遗余力
We go in fast and hard and we fight.
把他们打到趴
and we beat them down until they give up.
或死
or until they're dead.
他们都训练有素 武器精良
Look, they're well-trained and well-armed.
我们有些人可能会牺牲
Some of us might not make it back.
但我们会赢的
But we will win.
我们会击败坏人
We will take down the bad guys.
因为这是我们的工作
because that's what we do.
他们怕我们 嗯 很好
They're scared of us. Yeah. Good.
他们就该怕我们
They should be.
- 知道该去哪吗 - 嗯
- You know where we're goin'? - Yep.
准备好 10分钟后出发
‭Gear up. We roll out in 10.
准备好了吗
You ready?
- 不 我不去 - 什么
- Oh, no. I'm not goin'. - ‭What?
我腿伤成这样 我打不了仗
No, my leg busted up the way it is, I'm no good in a fight.
不论何时 受伤的迪恩·温彻斯特
I-I'll take a jacked up Dean Winchester.
也胜过任何10个猎人
over any 10 other Hunters any day.
是啊
Yeah.
我刚刚看到你了
I saw you.
你准备好了
You're ready for this.
你去让那些混蛋知道谁是老大
You show those sons of bitches who's boss.
那你呢 你要做什么
What about you? What are you gonna do?
我要救妈妈
I'm gonna save Mom.
如果她还在里面
Look, if she's in there,
如果我们真正的妈妈还在里面
if our real Mom is in there somewhere,
那我就要努力找到她 带她回来
then I'm gonna try and find her, bring her back.
- 唐娜 - 在一栋安全屋等着我
- Okay, Donna's - ‭Waiting for me at a safe house.
我要直接开过去 路上不能停
I should drive straight there, no stops.
等一切结束 你会给我打电话
And you'll call me when this is all over.
我知道
I got it.
- 乔迪 - 我会小心 我保证
- And, Jody - I'll be careful. I promise.
我不是想说这个
Not what I was gonna ask.
狠狠收拾他们
Kick it in the ass.
你行的
You got this.
过来
Come here.
你要回来
You come back.
我保证
Promise.
臭小子
Bitch.
- 混蛋 - 嗯
- Jerk. - ‭Yeah.
好了 你进入过我妈妈的脑袋
Okay, you got inside my Mom's head once before.
那我呢 能让我进去吗
What about me? You get me in?
你 我…
You? I…
或许吧
Perhaps.
但我需要我的设备
But I need my rig.
- 在哪 - 在基地
- Where is it? - ‭At the base.
但如果材料合适
But I suppose with the right materials,
我可以自己拼凑一下
I could cobble something together.
目标名单很快就发下去
Target lists will be distributed shortly.
在第二阶段中
In Phase Two,
百无禁忌
there are no restrictions.
家庭成员 路人
Family members, bystanders.
不要留下活口
Don't…leave…witnesses.
就这样
That will be all.
佩吉 查一下我们
Paige, I need you to pull up.
一位人员的位置
the location of one of our assets,
并且不要告诉别人
and I need you to keep it between us.
- 谁 - 玛丽·温彻斯特
- Who? - ‭Mary Winchester.
她在…
She's in…
（玛丽·温彻斯特）
堪萨斯州 黎巴嫩
Lebanon, Kansas.
好了 你需要的东西在哪
All right, where's the stuff you need?
应该在仓库里 地牢旁边
Should be in storage, next to the dungeon.
你以为我会让你溜出我的视线吗
Think I'm lettin' you out of my sight?
需要我提醒你 我的组织留下我等死吗
Need I remind you that my organization left me to die?
现在 我只站在我自己这边
At this point, I'm not on anyone's side but my own.
所以 我会帮你救你妈妈
So I help you try to save your mother,
等尘埃落定
and when the dust clears…
怎么 我放了你吗
What? I let you go?
我想再次见到我儿子
I'd like to see my son again.
我不是叫你饶过我
I'm not asking for a pass.
我只求让我先跑一会儿
I'm asking for a head start.
这些电极让你的δ波与玛丽同步
These electrodes sync your Delta waves with Mary's.
形成精神连接
forming a psychic link.
但要进入她的心智
But to enter her psyche.
会需要一定的专注和技艺
will take a certain measure of concentration and skill.
由于没时间教你如何达到
And as there's no time to teach you how to reach.
必须的治疗梦境
the necessary therapeutic dreamstate,
我要依靠这个
I'm banking on this.
混有强效镇定剂的催眠剂
Hypnotic agents laced with a potent sedative.
足以放倒一头大象了
It's enough to knock an elephant on its trunk.
不是吧
Really?
保险措施 你能理解吧
Little insurance. You understand.
这会疼的
This will hurt.
你能理解吧
You understand.
萨姆
Sam.
你醒了吗
Are you awake?
睡得香吗
How's the nap?
迪恩 午餐好了
Dean, lunch is ready.
妈妈
Mom.
我们得出去了 好吗
We gotta get out of here, okay?
你得跟我来
You need to come with me.
妈妈
Mom?
Mom.
妈妈
外面怎么回事
What is happening out there?
外围被突破
Perimeter's breached.
猎人
Hunters.
先生们
Gentlemen,
女士们
ladies,
你们知道该怎么做
you know what to do.
趴下
Get down!
我知道他们扰乱了你的心智
Look, I know that they messed with your head, okay?
我知道
I know it feels.
这里感觉更好
better in here.
更安全
It feels safer.
但我需要你听到我
But I-I need you to hear me.
我在想 或许我们稍后该带萨姆去公园
I was thinking maybe we should take Sammy to the park later,
在爸爸回家之前
before Daddy gets home.
好吗
Sound good?
妈妈 看着我
Mom, look at me.
这是你的选择
You're choosing this.
你最喜欢的
Your favorite.
太棒了
Yes!
你吃完的
After you eat.
我只想给你最好的 迪恩
I only want good things for you, Dean.
我绝不会让你有事的
I'll never let anything bad happen to you.
我恨你
I hate you.
上上上
Go, go, go, go, go.
上 快
Go! Hurry! Hurry!
你骗了我
You lied to me.
我那时还小
I was a kid.
你答应会保护我
You promised you'd keep me safe.
然后却跟亚撒色做了协议
And then you make a deal with Azazel.
是啊 那救了爸爸一命
Yeah, it saved Dad's life,
但我告诉你发生了什么
but I'll tell you something else that happened.
1983年11月2日
Because on November 2, 1983,
黄眼恶魔
old Yellow Eyes.
走进了萨姆的房间
came waltzing in to Sammy's room.
就因为你们的协议
because of your deal.
你抛下了我们
You left us.
我们孤独无助
Alone. ‭
因为爸爸已是行尸走肉
'Cause Dad was just a shell.
他的完美妻子 死了
His perfect wife? Gone.
我们完美的妈妈 这完美的家庭
Our perfect Mom, the perfect family…
都没了
was gone.
我
And I…
我只能
I had to be…
担起哥哥以外的职责
more than just a brother.
我要当爹
I had to be a father.
又当娘
and I had to be a mother,
好保护他
to keep him safe.
那不公平
And that wasn't fair.
我做不到
And I couldn't do it.
你想知道那是什么样子吗
And you wanna know what that was like?
他们杀了他爱的女人
They killed the girl that he loved.
他被路西法附身了
He got possessed by Lucifer.
他们在地狱里折磨他
They tortured him in Hell.
他失去了灵魂
And he lost his soul.
他的灵魂
His soul.
都因为你
All because of you.
这一切都是因为你
All of it was because of you.
我恨你
I hate you.
我也爱你
And I love you.
因为我 忍不住
'Cause I can't … I can't help it.
你是我妈妈
You're my Mom.
我理解
And I understand…
因为我也曾为了我所爱的人做协议
…'cause I have made deals to save the ones I love.
不止一次
more than once.
我原谅你
I forgive you.
我原谅一切
For all of it.
一切
Everything.
在另一边
On the other side of this,
我们可以重新开始
we can start over.
好吗
okay?
你 我 萨姆
You, me, Sam.
我们这次可以好好来过
We can get it right this time.
但我需要你抵抗
But I need you to fight.
现在 我需要你抵抗
Right now, I need you to fight.
我需要你 我需要你看我 妈妈
I need you … I need you to look at me, Mom.
我需要你好好看我 看到我
I need you to really look at me and see me.
妈妈 我需要你看到我
Mom, I need you to see me.
求你
Please.
迪恩
Dean?
妈妈
Mom.
- 不 - 没错
- No. - ‭Oh, yes.
怎么 以为能找回你妈妈吗
What? Thought you'd get your Mum back?
抱歉 迪恩 结局不是这样的
Sorry, Dean. Not how this ends.
结局是我了结你
This ends with me ending you.
我要杀了你
I'm gonna kill you. ‭
你不会的
‭You won't,
但我会很喜欢看你尝试
but I'd very much enjoy it if you tried.
你知道你妈妈怎么说你吗 迪恩
You want to know what your mother said about you, Dean?
我们那些
All those.
在路上猎魔的漫漫长日
long days and even longer nights.
和更加漫长的夜晚里
out on the road, hunting?
什么都没说过
Absolutely nothing.
这真好玩
This is fun.
- 让我来 - 嗯
- I got this. - ‭Yeah.
你把我们丢在地堡里时
When you left us alone in the bunker,
我早知道你是疯子
man, I knew you were psycho,
但我没想到你那么蠢
but I didn't think you were stupid.
我有很多特点
I may be many things…
但我不蠢
…but I'm not stupid.
妈妈
Mom?
玛丽
‭Mary.
我就知道你是个杀手
I knew you were a killer.
你们都是
You both are.
你说得对
You're right.
不惜代价
Whatever it takes …
开启一个传送门 让我离开这里
open a portal. Just get me the hell out of here.
恐怕我们现在没有
I'm afraid we don't have the resources.
进行撤离的资源
for an extraction at this moment.
别 别动
Don't! Don't.
听着 迪恩
Listen, Dean …
我是萨姆
It's Sam.
你是海斯吧
And you must be Hess, I trust.
你是这里的负责人
You're in charge of this whole operation?
或者说 这个烂摊子
Or, uh, what's left of it?
萨姆
Sam,
你或许认为杀我对你最有利
you might think it in your best interest to kill me,
结束这里的一切
to end all of this here.
但你现在杀我
But shooting me now,
切断跟英国记录者的一切联系
severing all ties with the British Men of Letters,
在这样的时刻
at this particular moment,
只会是天大的错误
that would be a grievous mistake.
我深表怀疑
I doubt it.
你有重新考虑的理由
There are reasons to reconsider.
你有些事不知道
Things that you don't know.
这是什么
What are these?
路西法回来了
Lucifer is back.
是的 萨姆
Yes, Sam.
都因为你的好朋友 克劳力
All thanks to your good friend Crowley.
虽然对他也没什么好处
Not that it did him much good.
克劳力死了
Crowley's dead.
魔鬼
And the Devil.
去找他儿子了
is out looking for his son,
跟随它母亲的脚步
following in its mother's footsteps,
追踪她和你的天使朋友
tracking her and your friend the angel.
如果路西法找到了那个孩子
If Lucifer gets his hands on that child,
他们会不可阻挡
they'll be unstoppable.
你不能单独去面对 你需要我们
You can't face that alone. You need us.
听她的 孩子
Listen to her, boy.
免了
Pass.
你个混蛋
You bastard.
找到些
Found some.
过期的止痛药
expired prescription painkillers, so…
真幸运
lucky me.
妈妈 你不用做那个 那不是你的事
Mom, you don't have to do that. It's not your job.
这
‭This…
这一切
All of this.
都是因为我
is because of me.
不会有事的
It'll be okay.
有事
It's not okay.
自从我回来
Since I've been back,
我知道我一直很疏离
I know… I've been distant.
甚至冷漠
Cold, even.
离开你们
Leaving you,
跟他们合作
working with them…
我是想做弥补
I was trying to make things right.
但是是远远地弥补 因为
Just from a distance, because…
跟你们在这里
being here with you.
实在太难
was too hard.
看到我对你
Seeing what I'd done.
对萨姆
to you.
造成的伤害 我…
and to Sam, I…
妈妈 你做的事
Mom, what you did,
那个协议
the deal…
一切
…everything.
此后发生的事
that's happened since.
都塑造了如今的我们
has made us who we are.
我们是什么人
And who we are?
我们很厉害
We kick ass.
我们拯救世界
We save the world.
萨姆呢
And Sam?
我好怕
I'm scared. What…
如果他不能原谅我呢
What if he can't forgive me?
妈妈
Mom.
你不用怕我
You don't have to be scared of me.
你回来太好了
Glad you're back, man.